<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LoanFaq</string>

    <string-array name="home1">
        <item>
            Thinking of buying your Dream Home? Compare and apply online at loanmantras.com to get instant e-approval for Home Loans
        Home loans not only help you realize your dreams of buying that house you have always wanted but also help save tax.
        But sometimes, the procedure of applying and getting a home loan can be complicated and frustrating.
        To avoid hassles and save cost, you must choose the right home loan.
        Buying your dream home is an important milestone in your life and requires a lot of planning, thinking and money,
        but with a wide variety of housing loans available in India,financing your dream home project is just a click away by low interest for home loan.
        Check your Home Loan eligibility now by filling up form and get best housing loan offers instantly.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="home2">
        <item>Why Apply for a Home Loan on loanmantras.com?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="home3">

        <item>Lowest interest rates: We have coordinated with HDFC Bank, ICICI Bank, Bajaj Finserv and Fullerton to get you the lowest home loan interest rates.</item>
        <item>Instant Quotes: Get quotes customized to your profile online instantly by filling in the form above.</item>
        <item>Simple Online Comparison: Compare personal loan offers on the basis of interest rate, EMI, processing fees and customer satisfaction.</item>
        <item>Transparency: Aimed at helping you make the right choice, we provide objective and transparent information about your loan options.</item>
        <item>Privacy: Your application is sent only to the lender you choose, and is never shared with anyone else.</item>
        <item>Trust: HDFC Bank and ICICI Bank India’s leading private sector banks, uses loanmantras.com – powered technology to give their customers the best loan.</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>
